KLAUDIA GOŁĘBIOWSKA

LOOKING FOR A FULL TIME JOB WHERE I CAN USE MY TECHNICAL SKILLS



PROFILE

A 25 years old student of Computer Science in Business and experienced PM & PMO is looking for a Junior/Intern position in analytics, data science or frontend. I am a professional, communicative individual with 7 years of experience in customer service, project, event and office management. I am looking for opportunities to use my knowledge of technology in a friendly environment.

- I have been learning about software applications and systems for three years,
- I completed an 8-month part-time study of Python at SDA (including modules in algorithms, databases, frontend and backend),
- I developed application projects in Visual Paradigm, where I played the role of an analyst, designing an object-oriented app in UML,
- · I created databases and data warehouses, using SQL Server Management Studio, I know the basics of MySQL and NoSQL,
- I designed and implemented frontend projects in the GitHub based on CSS, HTML & JavaScript.

In my professional work, I have participated in application testing, JavaScript and database training. I have references from employers from UK, Germany and Poland.

CONTACT



+ 48 796 707 205



K.GOLEBIOWSKA.AIM@GMAIL.COM



WROCLAW & REMOTE





GITHUB



PORTFOLIO

SKILLS

- HTML & CSS
- JavaScript
- UMI
- SQL
- GitHub
- Project Management & PMO
- Jira, Asana
- Scrum & Agile
- POSTMAN
- Bootstrap
- Django
- Python
- Testing
- Visual Paradigm
- SQL Server Management Studio
- ENGLISH B2 / C1 (IELTS)

EXPERIENCE

OPERATIONS PROJECT MANAGER

PYSZNE.PL - STO2 SP. Z O.O. | AUG 2020 - OCT 2020

I analyzed local projects to select the best logistics solutions and implement them nationally or globally. I implemented Asana for project management in Poland. (I did not extend my contract due to postcovid complications) | Poland & Netherlands

PM & PMO

3YOURMIND SP. Z O.O. | AUG 2019 - OCT 2020

Accounting & finance, events organizer, logistics, HR & administration, front office manager, office management, procurement, project manager | Berlin & Wroclaw

PROJECT MANAGER

CZAJKOWSKI SP. Z O.O. | JUN 2018 - JUN 2019

Contact with clients, problem-solving, supervision over documentation, sales and marketing activities within the project | Wroclaw

SENIOR ASSISTANT

AMBASSADOR THEATRE GROUP | APR 2016 - OCT 2017

Customer Success Team Leader, problem-solving, maintaining relations with customers in theatre | London

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SCIENCE IN BUSINESS

WROCLAW UNIVERSITY OF ECONOMICS | 2017-2022 WEEKEND STUDIES

CULTURAL AND SOCIETY

UNIVERSITY OF WROCLAW | 2017-2021 **EXTERNAL STUDIES**